There are customers out there who can’t find your business online.
Some directories have you listed, but others don’t. Or, they don’t have the right information.
Unfortunately, when you’re running a business, this is not your highest priority.
It’s not like it’s a giant billboard in a prime time location.
BUT with tons of directories online, having a listing on all of these sites, is like having billboards all over the city.
Trouble is, you’re probably too busy, and hiring a marketing consultant costs big bucks.
That’s where Town Center comes in; a one-stop solution for managing all of your online business profiles on all the big sites (Google+ Local, Facebook, Twitter, Yelp, Foursquare) and tons more.
All you have to do is install Town Center on your computer. Create your profile.  And then… walah… every single directory is updated automatically.
And whenever want to make a change, upload a picture, or even share a special offer, you just update your profile, click Sync Now, and the change is made everywhere.
Still not sure? Visit our site to do a test scan and see your current visibility scores.
You’ll be glad you did. And so will all your new happy customers.